Tyler Baxter

Lima, Ohio ● +1 419-604-0768 ● Ty.baxtr@gmail.com ● www.linkedin.com/tybaxter12/

Information Technology Support

Friendly and dependable customer service professional with over 2 years of experience. Well versed in administrative duties, problem-solving, planning, and time management. Experienced with working in fast-paced environments and working directly with a diverse range of clients. Knowledable in handling confidential matters and proprietary information.

LICENSES/CERTIFICATIONS

Life Insurance License

Jan 2021 - May 2022

State of Ohio

Electrician Apr 2016 - May 2021

State of Ohio Apprenticeship Council

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Technical Skills: Customer Communication Management, Customer Service, Documentation, Hardware Knowledge, Microsoft 365, Network Basics, Installation & Configuration, Technical Troubleshooting

Soft Skills: Adaptability, Attention to Detail, Dependability, Friendliness, Interpersonal Skills, Planning/Processing, Prioritization, Problem Solving, Time Management

Hobbies: Backpacking, Camping, Circuit Racing, Continuous Education, Drift Racing, Hiking, Video Game Development, Video Game Testing

Personality Interests: Computer Hardware Enthusias , Meditation, Robotics, Technology Advancements, Traveling

WORK EXPERIENCE

Journeyman Electrician • Dayton, OH • Full-time International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers LU 82

July 2023 - Present

- Licensed in the state of Ohio as a Journeyman Electrician
- Experience in Residential, Commercial, and Industrial electrician installations
- Reading schematics and laying out installations for employees. Received positive feedback and commendation from clients

Licensed Life Insurnace Sr. Field Underwriter • Lima, OH, USA Apr 2021 - May 2023 Equis Financial

- Daily interpersonal people skills
- Schedule and coordinate meetings with clients daily
- Communicate with clients about their mortgage protection options
- · Help clients complete and submit applications to carriers and follow through the underwriting process
- Service client future policy needs

Electrician • Lima, OH, USA 2022International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers LU 32

Apr 2016 - May 2021

- UZZINTERNATIONAI BROTNERNOOG OT EIECTRICAI WORKERS LU 32
 - Licensed in the state of Ohio as a Journeyman Electrician
 Experience in Residential, Commercial, and Industrial electrician installations
 - Reading & Writing Schematics

• Proficient with the direct installation of wiring at construction and other sites

EDUCATION

Electrical in Journeyman Electrician

NJATC - National Joint Apprenticeship Training Center • Lima, OH • GPA: 2nd in Class Apr 2016 - Apr 2022

- Northwest Community College Curriculum Partnership
- State of Ohio Apprenticeship Council

High School Graduate

Bath High school • Lima, OH